[
  {
    "question": "Who was the mother of Moses?",
    "options": [
      "Sarah",
      "Leah",
      "Hannah",
      "Jochebed"
    ],
    "answer": "Jochebed"
  },
  {
    "question": "What river was Moses placed into as a baby?",
    "options": [
      "Nile River",
      "Jordan River",
      "Red Sea",
      "Euphrates River"
    ],
    "answer": "Nile River"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Moses\u2019 mother put him in before placing him in the river?",
    "options": [
      "A boat",
      "A jar",
      "A basket",
      "A box"
    ],
    "answer": "A basket"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who found baby Moses in the river?",
    "options": [
      "Queen of Egypt",
      "Pharaoh\u2019s daughter",
      "His sister Miriam",
      "A servant girl"
    ],
    "answer": "Pharaoh\u2019s daughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who helped take care of baby Moses after he was found?",
    "options": [
      "His aunt",
      "His sister, Miriam",
      "Pharaoh\u2019s wife",
      "A nurse from Egypt"
    ],
    "answer": "His sister, Miriam"
  },
  {
    "question": "What job did Moses\u2019 real mother have when he was a baby in the palace?",
    "options": [
      "Cook",
      "Servant",
      "His nurse",
      "Teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "His nurse"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the name Moses mean?",
    "options": [
      "Drawn out of the water",
      "Saved from danger",
      "Gift of God",
      "Born in a basket"
    ],
    "answer": "Drawn out of the water"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was Moses born?",
    "options": [
      "Canaan",
      "Midian",
      "Israel",
      "Egypt"
    ],
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the king ruling Egypt when Moses was born?",
    "options": [
      "Nebuchadnezzar",
      "Herod",
      "Pharaoh",
      "Caesar"
    ],
    "answer": "Pharaoh"
  },
  {
    "question": "What cruel order did Pharaoh give about Hebrew baby boys?",
    "options": [
      "To send them to the palace",
      "To give them to Egyptians",
      "To throw them in the river",
      "To take them to the desert"
    ],
    "answer": "To throw them in the river"
  }
]